Guide to the Clarence Stein papers, 1905-1983.
Stein, Clarence papers
- Series V. Research File
  - Early Writings and Articles (unpublished)
    - "VIII -- 1918-1921 Reports of Housing Committee" (Box 11, Folder 27)
      political platform, housing, city planning, war housing
      1918-1921
      New York Labor Party, Reconstruction Commission
  - Letter box entitled: USA -- Research -- TVA
    - T.V.A. C..S.S. 1962 Notes (Box 11, Folder 28)
      coordinated development, power system
      1962-1964
      notes, outlines, graphs
    - T.V.A. Reference Material, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      flood control, mailing addresses, history, Melton Hill Reservoir and Land use development, reservoir systems and power, forestry
      1956, 1958, 1960-1962
      pamphlets, articles, maps
  - U.S.A. Research
    - T.V.A. Reference Material, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      industrial growth and river traffic, dams and reservoirs, annual report (1962), water resources, T.V.A. operations
      1960-1962, undated
      pamphlets, notes, maps
    - T.V.A. Industrial Development (Box 11, Folder 31)
      Aubrey J. Wagner (Chairman of NA Board)
      1960,1963
      notes, correspondence, maps
    - Regional Cities, Hartford, 9 IX '57 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      dispersal
    - Employment -- Dispersal, N.Y., Executive Offices and Research Laboratories Industrial Parks and Estates, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      Westchester County Tour
      Frederick Clark, Hugh Pomeroy
      1954, 1958, 1960
      notes, article, photographs, map
  - U.S.A. Research
    - Office Bid. and Laboratories, Dispersal (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - U.S.A. Research
    - Westchester (Box 12, Folder 1)
      executive offices and research laboratories
      Hugh R. Pomeroy (Director, Westchester County Department of Planning)
      reports, reference lists, correspondence, notes, outline
    - Westchester Offices and Labs (Visited) (Box 12, Folder 2)
      executive offices and research laboratories survey
      Hugh R. Pomeroy
      correspondence, outlines, maps
  - U.S.A. Research
    - New Haven Redevelopment (Box 12, Folder 3)
      1956-1961
      notes, reports, articles, pamphlets
    - Executive Offices And Research Laboratories (Box 12, Folder 4)
      study for New Canaan, Conn,
      Frederick P. Clark (consultant)
  - U.S.A. Research
    - [Untitled] (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Chatham Village, factories planned for people business planning and architecture
      articles, reprint, clippings
    - "Economic Advantages And Disadvantages of Metropolitan Concentration" (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Sargant Florence (Prof., University of Birmingham)
    - Industrial Parks -- Insurance Co. -- Dispersal Also Insurance Co. Dispersal (Box 12, Folder 7)
      1960, 1963
      notes, correspondence, article
  - U.S.A. Research
    - [Untitled] (Box 12, Folder 8)
      industrial park listing, state of Pennsylvania, General Motors
      1960-1961, undated
      Resources for the Future, Inc.
      annual report, pamphlets, list
  - Foreign Research for New Towns
    - Stockholm-- The Summer City (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Erik Asklund
      1947
      soft cover travel booklet
    - Sweden (Foreign Housing and Planning) (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Donald and Astrid Monson
      postcards, articles
    - Stockholm Regional Plan (not all in English) (Box 12, Folder 11)
      1958
      booklet, notes
    - "Building A City and a Metropolis" (Box 12, Folder 12)
      planned development of Stockholm
      Yngve Larsson
      1962-1963
      reprint and notes
    - Sweden. Motes 1960-62. Addresses (Box 12, Folder 13)
      1960-1962
      notes, addresses
    - Stockholm -- Sweden -- 1960 (not all in English) (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Farsta, Stockholm City, Vallingby Center
      1954, 1959-1960
      pamphlets, maps, brochures
  - Foreign Research For New Towns
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Royal Palace of Stockholm, Den Offentliga Parken (parks?)
      1948, 1950
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Swedish shopping centers, Stockholm regional plan, housing, satellite towns of Stockholm
      1956, I960, 1962, undated
      pamphlets, articles, map
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Swedish architecture, housing, cooperative housing, Vallingby
      1948-1949, 1952
      pamphlets, book
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 12, Folder 18)
      new Swedish architecture, Farsta Center, a shopping center, sculpture, Arsta, reconstruction work
      Yngve Larsson, Goran Sidenbladh
      1955, 1959-1962
      articles, pamphlets
    - Arsta Stockholm Sweden (from Sidenbladh) (Box 12, Folder 19)
      J.H. Martin, Goran Sidenbladh
      1953-1954
      drawings, correspondence, photographs
    - [Vallingby] (Box 12, Folder 20)
      satellite suburb town of Stockholm
      J.H. Martin
      1949, 1952, 1954-1955, 1958
      manuscript notes, revisions, outlines, correspondence, drawings, pamphlet material, photographs, article
  - [Sweden] Foreign Research, for New Towns
    - Vallingby Material (not all in English) (Box 12, Folder 21)
      satellite suburb
      J.H. Martin, G. Sidenbladh
      1951-1953, 1956, 1963
      pamphlets, maps, correspondence, manuscript notes, reports, photographs, outlines
    - [from Martin] (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Vallingby
      1955, 1960
    - Orebro Sweden, Baronbackarna, Markbacken (Box 12, Folder 23)
      Radburn idea, new housing developments
      1960, undated
      outlines, drawings, notes, correspondence
    - Gothenburg -- Sweden -- Photographs, Plans, R-L (Box 12, Folder 24)
      1949-1950, undated
      plans, correspondence, photographs, clippings, postcards
  - Foreign Research For New Towns
    - [Untitled] (Box 12, Folder 25)
      New Towns, garden cities, Welwyn, Letchword, London New Towns
      Sir Frederic Osborn
      1912, 1924, 1946, 1954, 1958, 1960
      New Towns Committee, Ministry of Town and Count Planning, Dept. of Health for Scotland
      articles, maps, manuscript notes, reports
    - Housing and Planning in Great Britain, C.S. Stein, X-50 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      County of London Plan comments by C.S. Stein
    - London County Council -- 1954 and 1962 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      local government for Greater London, expanded towns, L.C.C. Architects
      Albert Mayer, Leslie Martin
      1954, 1956, 1959, 1961-1962
      notes, articles, correspondence, reprints
    - Greater London Notes (Box 12, Folder 28)
      London's office growth, Town Development Act of 1952, London County Council
      1951-1962, undated
      notes, article
  - Foreign Research for New Towns
    - "Design In Town And Village" (Box 12, Folder 29)
      design in building layout and grouping
      Frederick Gribbard, W.G. Holford, Thomas Sharp
      Ministry of Housing and local Government
      soft-bound book
    - Industry in New Towns (Box 12, Folder 30)
      1951, 1954
      articles, reprints, manuscript notes
    - Industrial Town, Lew Wilson, Correspondence T'x 54 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      British Industrial Trading Estates, industrial development
      correspondence, bibliography, manuscripts notes
    - New Towns, Industry (Box 12, Folder 32)
      British industrial estates, Harlow, Kernel Hemstead
      1948, 1950, 1954, 1959
      minutes, manuscript notes, articles
    - New Towns Basic Program and How Carried Out (Box 12, Folder 33)
      local employment, green belt, ownership of land, balanced communities, Stevenage, Harlow, government policy
      Sir Frederick Osborne, R.S. McDougall, W. Eric Adams
      1954, 1960
      Meadowvale Developments Limited
      correspondence, manuscript notes, charts
    - New Towns in G.B., 1954, #2 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      Bracknell, Kernel Hempstead, Stevenage, Crowley Harbor
      notes, reports
    - NTs in GB -- NOTES '54 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      limitations restricting New Towns, Harlow
      bibliography, manuscript notes, correspondence, outlines, memo
    - NT -- GB Manuscript Notes of Clarence Stein, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      1954-1955
      manuscripts notes, drafts and revisions
    - "The British New Towns Policy" (Box 12, Folder 37)
      Sir Frederic J. Osborn
      reprint
    - [Untitled] (Box 12, Folder 38)
      British Land Commission Bill, New Towns Outline
      1959, 1964, 1967
      articles, reprints, outlines, clippings, pamphlets
    - England Radburn Idea, L.C.C. -- Rochampton, Sights of London, New Towns, Stevenage Center (Box 12, Folder 39)
      Anthony B. Davies (Chief Architect ), Paul Ritter
      drawings, articles, photographs, correspondence plans
    - [Untitled] (Box 12, Folder 40)
      New Towns, housing density and town design
      1960, 1962-1963, 1966
      notes, articles, clippings
    - New Towns in G.R. (sic), Definition, Higher Education (Box 12, Folder 41)
      clippings, manuscript notes
    - New Towns 1960 For Talk at A. I. P., October 24, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      garden cities, financing, what has happened to NT concept, impressions, industrial development, housing, financing
      W.O. Hart (General Manager, H-H), Albert Mayer, Raymond Unwin, W. Eric Adams
      1923, 1950, 1953-1954, 1960-1961, 1963
      articles, outlines, manuscript notes, revisions, correspondence
    - New Towns Great Britain (Box 12, Folder 43)
      New Towns, future ownership, Town Development Act, metropolitan areas
      1945, 1951, 1954, 1959, 1960, 1962, 1963, 1967
      Royal Commission on The Distribution of the Industrial Population, Town and Country Planning Association
      report, articles
  - Foreign Research for New Towns, Great Britain.
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 1)
      new schools, playing fields, Workingham School, primary school planning
      S.A.W. Johnson-Marshall (Chief Architect)
      1949-1952, 1955
      Ministry of Education
      articles in pamphlets
  - Foreign Research for New Towns
    - Cambridge (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Cambridge Plan
      news clipping
  - G.B. New Towns
    - Corby New Town (Box 13, Folder 3)
      New Towns, Great Britain
      William Holford, H. Myles Wright
      1951
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 4)
      development and redevelopment of N.T. 's Coventry and Forest Park, Ohio
      1958, 1960-1961, undated
      pamphlets, correspondence, clippings
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Coventry: development plan for city road pattern, housing units
      Arthur Ling (City architect)
      1961-1962, undated
      reports, clippings, descriptive booklet
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 6)
      preliminary planning proposals for Cumbernauld New Town
      1958-1959
    - Harlow N.T. (see Industry (H for E), NTS in GB in 54 (CSS) for W. Eric Adams Summary, Pamphlets (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Frederick Gibberd (architect), W. Eric Adams (General Manager, Harlow Development Corporation)
      articles, clippings, correspondence, manuscript notes
  - Foreign Research for New Towns
    - Hemel -- Hemstead, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      H. Kellett Ablett (Chief Architect)
      1960, 1962
      plans, maps, correspondence, master plan, notes, pamphlet
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Runcorn, Letchworth
      1960, 1966
      maps, articles
    - Stepney -- Poplar, England (London) (Box 13, Folder 10)
      redevelopment in England
      London County Council
      press release, map, photographs
    - Stevenage: Material under "CSS: Actual Past Jobs, File 2g Drawer 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      1959
    - New Towns -- Scotland, East Kilbridge, Cumbernaud (Box 13, Folder 12)
      1961, undated
      articles, drawings
    - Israel: Up to, not including, 1959 trip (Box 13, Folder 13)
      planning and architecture, impressions of Israel, housing, regional landscape design, comments re TNTA
      Artur Glikson, Arieh Sharon, Albert Mayer, Harold Robinson (Regional Housing Advisor, International Corporation Administration), Benton MacKaye
      1949-1954, 1956-1957, 1959
      Israel Town Planning Association
      correspondence, memos, article
  - Foreign Research For New Towns
    - [not all in english] (Box 13, Folder 14)
      physical planning in Israel
      Arieh Sharon
      hardcover book, correspondence, translated pamphlet
    - Regional Planning and Development (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Artur Glikson, author
      Netherlands Universities Foundation for International Cooperation
      Location:
      The Hague
    - Some Problems of Housing in Israel's New Towns and Suburbs (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Artur Glikson
    - Urban Land Use In Residential Quarters (Box 13, Folder 17)
      lecture
    - Israel-- 1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      planning and development, bibliography of Israel
      Artur Glikson/ Arieh Sharon
      1959, 1961
      correspondence, reprints, pamphlets
    - Planned Development in Israel (Box 13, Folder 19)
      outline, report
    - Israel Plans A Nation -- Notes (Box 13, Folder 20)
      manuscript notes, manuscript drafts, revisions; correspondence
    - Israel Plans A Nation (Box 13, Folder 21)
      national planned development
      outline, manuscript notes, correspondence, program
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 13, Folder 22)
      regional planning and technology, collective settlements in Israel
      Artur Glikson, Arieh Sharon
      reprints, pamphlets
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 13, Folder 23)
      rural planning and development in Israel
      Artur Glikson, Werner Wolff
      1958, 1961
      report, article
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 24)
      agricultural settlement, public ownership, experimental habitational unit, etc.
      Artur Glikson, Avraham Harman
      1958, undated
      bibliography for box, pamphlets, notes
  - Foreign Research For New Towns
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 25)
      national sovereignty, industry, the Negev, planning, housing, health, education
      Y. Tamir (Ministry of Labour, Housing Director
      1949, 1956, 1958-1959
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 26)
      Israel's future, Beilinson Hospital, water development, Negev railway, architecture, urban housing
    - Israel, Maps and Plans of Cities, Beersheba, Proposal of A. Klein (Box 13, Folder 27)
      A. Glikson (Chief Architect)
      1947, 1956-1957
      maps, drawing, memorandum
  - Foreign Research For New Towns
    - Nazareth -- New Town, Plans and Photographs, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      plans, photographs, clippings
    - Illustrations Clippings (Box 13, Folder 29)
      Israel and science, teaching hospital, architecture, immigration
      1955, 1959
    - Photo of Museum, Jerusalem (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Al. Mansfield
      ca. 1959
      photo
  - Letter box entitled Denmark, Finland, and Norway and Holland
    - City Plan Vest with an English summary (not all in English) (Box 13, Folder 31)
      city plan of Copenhagen, Denmark
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 13, Folder 32)
      Copenhagen planning: preliminary outline, status, regulations, summaries
      1947-1949, 1952, 1960-1962
      Copenhagen Regional Planning Office
      reports, maps, correspondence
    - [Untitled] (not all in English) (Box 13, Folder 33)
      regional planning of Copenhagen, urban cooperation in Denmark
      1954, 1957, 1966
      articles, report
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 34)
      town planning in Denmark; Stein in Denmark; promotional material for Louisiana, Denmark
      1955-1956, 1959-1961
      articles, pamphlets, reports, maps, financial statements, brochures
  - Foreign Research For New Towns
    - [Unititled] (not all in English) (Box 13, Folder 35)
      collective houses, Sogard, Soborg, Sondergard Park, Scandinavian housing, Denmark
      Eric Carlson
      1951-1952, 1963, undated
      Ministry of Housing, Denmark
      pamphlets, correspondence, map, news clipping
    - Socialt Boligbyggeri (not in English) (Box 13, Folder 36)
      Copenhagen
      c_. 1941
    - The Architecture of Denmark (Box 13, Folder 37)
      The Architectural Press
    - [Untitled] (language, location, unknown) (Box 13, Folder 38)
      map plan
    - Tapiola -- G -- C -- Finland (Box 13, Folder 39)
      publicity, plans for Finnish new town
      Albert Mayer, Heiffi von Hertzen
      notes, pamphlets, correspondence, clipping
    - [Untitled] (Box 13, Folder 40)
      Tapiola Garden City Finland
      Housing Foundation Asuntosaatio (planner and builder)
      mounted photographs
    - Organization Charts, Plan (not all in English (Box 13, Folder 41)
      Amsterdam developmental plan, maps of Rotterdam, physical planning in The Netherlands
      1955, 1961, 1963
      charts, report, maps, pamphlet
    - The Story of Rotterdam (Box 13, Folder 42)
      Rotterdam
      Hans Reinhardt (author)
    - Senri New Town (Box 13, Folder 43)
      Public Enterprise Bureau, Osaka Perfectual Government Japan
      brochure
- Series VI. Correspondence Files
  - Requests For Help (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Carl E. Killer (Dean, Queens College School of General Studies)
    1969-1970
  - Requests For Info and Advice For Reading on Planning and to Students (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Paul Ritter
    1947, 1961, 1964-1965, 1967-1969
  - A -- General (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Robert Alexander, Tracy B. Augur, Carol Aronovici, W. Eric Adams, (Managing Director Meadowvale Developments, L.A., Charles Abrams (Chairman NYS Commission Against Discrimination)
    1947, 1950-1957, 1959-1960, 1962-1964, 1966-1967
    correspondence, clippings
  - Alaska (Box 14, Folder 4)
    newtown development
    report notes
  - Rampart Canyon Dam (Box 14, Folder 5)
    proposed new town in Alaska
    Ivan Block
    1957, 1962-1963
    Ivan Block and Associates
    report notes, maps, correspondence, clipping, memorandum
  - A. I. A. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Joseph Watterson (Editor, Journal of the A. I. A. George Bain Cummings (President, A. I. A.), John Nobel Richards (President, A. I. A.)
    1951, 1954-1955, 1959, 1961-1964, 1966-1967, 1969-1970
    American Institute of Architects, A. I. A. Committee on Urban Design and Housing
    listings, articles, correspondence, clipping
  - A. I. A. Committee On Fellows, 1959-1961 to 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    nominations and endorsements
    G.E. Kidder Smith
    1958-1962, 1965
    Jury of Fellows, Committee on Fellows
  - Co mm- -Community Planning AIA 1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Carl Feiss (Chairman)
    1956, 1959
    correspondence, reports, notes, speech, outlines
  - AIA New York Chapter, Civic Des. Comm. including Simon Breines, Milton Glass, Chairman (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Morris Ketchum, Jr. (President) Paul D. Spreiregen (Director, Urban Design Programs)
    1961-1963, 1966
    Housing and Home Finance Agency, National Housing Conference, Inc.
    correspondence, notes, articles, press release newsletters
  - N.Y. Chapter AIA Research Study 1961 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    re redevelopment of residential neighborhoods for middle income families
    Henry Whitney
    correspondence, proposals, notes
  - Woodbridge AIA -- NY Chapter (Box 14, Folder 11)
    roposed
    F.J. Woodbridge (President, N.Y. Chapter, A. I. A.
  - A. I. A. Urban Design Committee (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Arch R. Winter (Chairman), Carl Feiss, Henry S. Churchill
    1950, 1961-1963, 1965
    correspondence, program drafts, memo, minutes, articles, notes
  - AIA Urban Planning Committee, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    1956, 1959-1961
    Community Planning Committee
    minutes, correspondence, memos
  - AIP (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Robert L. Williams (Exec. Director, AIP), G. Holmes Perkins (Dean, School of Fine Arts, U. of Penn.)
    1958-1961, 1966-1967
  - ASPO [American Society of Planning Officials] (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Dennis O' Harrow (Exec. Director)
    1952-1953, 1955, 1958, 1960, 1962, 1964
    correspondence, award certificates, program
  - Ames -- E&M (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Edmund T. Ames, Muriel Ames
    1963-1965, 1967-1968
    correspondence, articles, notes
  - Architectural Licence--Cal. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Robert K. Kelley (Exec. Secretary, State Board of Architectural Examiners)
  - Arensberg (Walter) Collection 1940-c_. 1945 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    William W. Wurster, Mrs. Walker A. Haas
    1940-1941, 1944-1945, 1947-1949, 1953
    correspondence, drawings, notes, articles, resume
  - C. Asher (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Charles Ascher, Herbert Emmerich, Louis Brown low
    1957, 1962-1963, 1965-1967, 1969-1970
  - Australia (Box 14, Folder 20)
    J.A. Hepburn (Town Planning Commissioner, Perth, W. Australia)
    1955, 1957, 1962, 1966
    correspondence, legislative bill
  - B (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Karl J. Belsar, Harvey Broome (Wilderness Society), Edmund N. Bacon (Exec. Dir., City Planning Commission, Philadelphia, Pa.), Milton Breivogel (Director of Planning, L.A. County Regional Plan Commission), Margaret W. Barnard, Frederick Bigger, Ivan Bloch, Russell VanNest Black, Simon Breines, Algernon D. Black (Encampment for Citizenship), Jack Bevash, Peter Bing
    1955, 1958-1969
    Baltimore Regional Planning Council
  - Bauer, Catherine (Mr. and Mrs. Wm. W. Wurster) (Box 14, Folder 22)
    1940-1944, 1946, 1948-1951, 1953, 1955, 1959-1961, 1963-1964, 1968
    articles, correspondence, newsletters, clippings
  - Baughman, Marjie 1968 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    doctoral candidate, Radburn
    1968-1969
    articles, photographs, correspondence
  - Beaux Arts [Institute of Design] (Box 14, Folder 24)
    1952
    correspondence, drafts, memos
  - Blackham, Louise (Box 14, Folder 25)
    1953, 1955, 1957-1960, 1962-1963
    Corporation of the District of Kitimat, Civic Unity Committee of Seattle, City of Seattle Planning Committee
    correspondence, map, clipping
  - Books Ordered (Box 14, Folder 26)
    Marie McGuire (Commissioner, Public Housing Administration )
    1962-1968
    University of Illinois Press
    correspondence, invoices
  - C -- Misc. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    Stuart Chase, Elizabeth Coit, Walter Creese (School of Architecture and Allied Arts, Univ. of Oregon), Harry F. Cunningham, Elliott L. Chisling
    1949-1953, 1958-1959, 1961-1965, 1967, 1972
    City Housing Corporation, Sunnyside Properties, Inc.
    correspondence, notices
  - To California (Box 14, Folder 28)
    addresses in Washington, California
    Karl Belser
    1963-1965, undated
    notes, report, correspondence
  - California (Box 14, Folder 29)
    San Diego, San Francisco-Berkeley, Los Angeles, Conejo
    1963-1964, 1966, undated
  - Canada -- Alan H. Armstrong, Adams, Humphrey Carver, Hancock, etc. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    A.J. Dankin (Professor and Head of Division of Regional and Town Planning, School of Architecture, Univ. of Toronto, Canada), A.H. Armstrong (Ad. of Comm. Planning, Central Mortgage and Housing Corp., Ottawa, Canada), Eric Beecroft (Dir., C.P Assn. of Canada), Humphrey Carver (Chairman, Research Committee c )
    1950-1953, 1955-1958, 1960-1961, 1963, 1967
    Central Mortgage and Housing Corporation, Town Planning Institute of Canada, School of Architecture, University of Toronto, Community Planning Association of Canada
    correspondence, article, program, membership cards
  - Canada: Alan H. Armstrong, Adams, Humphrey Carver, Hancock, etc. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    planning Toronto, municipality of Metro Toronto Act. new towns--Canada
    Macklin L. Hancock (President, PPAL), W. Eric Adams
    1961, 1963-1964
    Project Planning Associates Ltd.
    correspondence, pamphlets, legislative bills, articles, notes, soft cover book, outline, map
  - Canada National Gallery Ottawa (Box 14, Folder 32)
    1951, 1953
  - Carlson, Eric (Chief,Housing Section, Center for Housing, Building and Planning, United Nations, N.Y., Foundation for Cooperative Housing, Inc., Inter-American Housing and Planning Center, Assoc. Editor, "The American City") (Box 14, Folder 33)
    housing projects, and programs